http://www.tbco.net/privacy-policy

Locations in MO and KS!HomeAbout UsMeet the TeamChambers of CommercePrivacy PolicyCareersServicesTax AuditBusiness AdvisoryBusiness PlanningNonprofitQuickBooks Pro AdvisorResourcesCOVID-19 TAX PLANNINGQuick LinksReviewsLocationsHarrisonville, MOOlathe, KSBlogPay OnlineMoreHomeAbout UsMeet the TeamChambers of CommercePrivacy PolicyCareersServicesTax AuditBusiness AdvisoryBusiness PlanningNonprofitQuickBooks Pro AdvisorResourcesCOVID-19 TAX PLANNINGQuick LinksReviewsLocationsHarrisonville, MOOlathe, KSBlogPay OnlineLocations in MO and KS!HomeAbout UsServicesResourcesReviewsLocationsBlogPay Online
Troutt, Beeman & Co., P.C. Privacy Policy
CPAs, providing financial services, such as estate and tax planning, to individuals are required by federal law to inform their clients of their policies regarding privacy of client information.  CPAs have been and continue to be bound by professional standards of confidentiality that are even more stringent than those required by law.  Therefore, we have always safeguarded the confidentiality of information provided to us by our clients and have protected your right to privacy.Types of Nonpublic Personal Information We Collect
We collect non-public personal information about you - but only when that information is provided by you or is obtained by us with your authorization. Parties to Whom We Disclose Information
As a general rule, we do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our clients or former clients to anyone.  However, to the extent permitted by law and any applicable code of Professional Conduct, certain nonpublic information about you may be disclosed in the following situations:
To comply with a validly issued and enforceable subpoena or summons.
In the course of a review of our firm's practices under the authorization of a state or national licensing board, or as necessary to properly respond to an inquiry or complaint from such licensing board.
In conjunction with a prospective purchase, sale or merger for all or a part of our practice, provided that we obtain a written confidentiality agreement from the prospective purchaser or merger partner.
As part of any actual or threatened legal proceedings or alternative dispute resolution proceedings provided we disclose only the information necessary to file, pursue or defend the lawsuit and take reasonable precautions to ensure that the information disclosed does not become a matter of public record.
Protecting the Confidentiality and Security of Current and Former Clients’ Information
We retain records relating to professional services that we provide so that we are better able to assist you with your professional needs and, in some cases, to comply with professional guidelines.  In order to guard your nonpublic personal information, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable laws and regulations.  Please email info@tbco.net or call 816-380-5500 if you have any questions, because your privacy, our professional ethics, and the ability to provide you with quality financial services are very important to us.
Copyright © 2019 TBCO - All Rights Reserved.  Privacy Policy
